翻譯: Jamie sumsmit Amber
嘿 親愛的 你看起來真棒
Oh, hey, honey. You look sharp.
- 今天穿上了戰靴啊  - 哦 這雙嗎
- Got your power heels on. - Oh, these?
校對: 不賣萌斯基
沒啊 就是很普通的
No, these are just regular
哪都能買到的樂福鞋
men's loafers you can buy in any store.
不過我加了三四個鞋墊 更方便我做這個
And I put three or four insoles in so it's easier to do this.
后期: UU123
- 找個房間啦  - 這都是我們的房間
- Ugh, get a room. - Hey, these are all our rooms.
壓制: B B
你才該去找個房間 說真的 你怎么穿起正裝了
You get a room. Seriously, why are you dressed up?
Harris打給我
Oh, Harris called me in.
說幫我安排了個重要采訪
He finally set up a big interview for me.
今晚我可以問些刁鉆問題了
Tonight, I get to ask the tough questions.
爸你要采訪誰呢
Who are you interviewing,Dad?
沒問 也許我該問的
Didn't ask. Probably should've.
這真是個刁鉆問題
Tough questions start now.
- 你  - 你這是登岸休假嗎 海員寶貝
- You... - Are you on shore leave, honey?
今天在體育館考完游泳后 一打開儲物柜
It was swim test day in gym, and when I got back to my locker,
里面只有這套東西
this was all that was left in there.
聽起來像是高手所為
Sounds like some smooth criminal
挑這天完美作案 收買門衛然后偷走你的運動包
picked a perfect day to bribe the janitors to swipe your gym bag.
整蠱成功 你被耍了
Sha-boof! You've been pranked.
我穿成這樣坐地鐵回來的 丟臉死了
I had to ride the subway like this. It sucked!
不過有個老太太說謝謝我的服務
Although a nice old woman did thank me for my service.
下次記住別再吃掉最后一根奶酪棒了
Next time, don't take the last mozzarella stick.
害我像只野獸一樣在干喝醬料
I had to drink the sauce like an animal.
就是因為這個嗎 好的
That's what this is about? Fine.
你想開戰是吧 奉陪到底
You want a prank war? You got a prank war!
你在玉米花生糖盒子上美極了
Loved you on the cracker jack box.
爆米花品牌 包裝上有個水手
- 瞧我這聰明才智  - 工作找得怎樣了 Ian
- Upstairs.  - How's the job search going, Ian?
- 還沒收到你給的租金  - 馬上就成了
- Still haven't got that rent check.  - I'm all over it.
在我等著我的公司變現的同時
While I'm waiting for my company to monetize,
我也在找合適的正職
I'm searching for the perfect day job.
我把簡歷放上了鄰客音 就讓那些公司爭破頭吧
I posted my resume on Linkedin. Let the feeding frenzy begin.
世界上最大的專業網絡社交平臺
給我個臺階下好嘛
You gonna help me out with this?
這個恩情我會記住的 兄弟
I won't forget that, buddy.
各位 壞消息
Guys, bad news.
我之前很想進的那個作家小組
That writers' group I've been trying to get into?
- 同意我加入了  - 我要說你總會度過這關的嗎
- They accepted me. - You'll get past this?
不是 我每月要招待他們一次
No, I have to host these guys once a month.
我可不能讓那些出版作家們坐在一張
I can't have published writers sitting on a couch
在學校垃圾桶撿回來的破沙發上
I found in a dumpster in college.
我們可是從浣熊手中搶過來的啊
We fought off raccoons for that thing.
的確 若是二十多歲 有張浣熊沙發還說得過去
Exactly. And while it may be cute to have a raccoon
不過現在我的腳趾已然要邁過三十大關了
couch in your 20s, I'm dipping my toe into my 30s...
- 你的腳趾有十二年那么長啊  - 我說真的 Michael
- Your toe is 12 years long? - I'm serious, Michael.
這個作家組會是我的巨大轉機
This group could be my big break.
我也不想求你們的 可沙發確實比較貴
And you know I hate to ask, but couches are expensive.
你們看能不能借我點...
So maybe you could just loan me a little...
我的文稿經紀人來電話了
Oh, hey. It's my literary agent.
嘿 Vernon
Hey, Vernon.
她總無事不登三寶殿
Every time she comes up here, she wants something.
而我總對她有求必應
And every time she comes up here, I end up giving it to her.
這次我要打破這個惡性循環
I gotta break this cycle of dependency.
Mike 你知道每次對Leigh說"不"都有什么后果嗎
Mike, you know what happens when you say "No" To Leigh.
總是小事化大
The problem just becomes bigger.
還記得那次你拒絕付錢給她的人生導師嗎
Remember when you refused to pay for her life coach?
- 那個后來進了康復院的嗎  - 對 她很傷心
- The one who ended up in rehab? - Yes, she was so upset,
以至后來你得為她的哀傷心理治療師付錢
you had to pay for her grief counselor.
那個后來自殺的家伙嗎
The one who killed himself?
給她買沙發吧 Mike
Just please buy the couch, Mike.
我的經紀人不干了 要去當口腔保健專家
Well, my agent is leaving me to become a dental hygienist.
"他寧愿看別人的口腔
"He'd rather look at the
也不愿看我的文章"
inside of people's mouths than my writing."
- 這是他的原話  - 也許你去還能打折呢
- That was a quote.  - Maybe you'll get a discount?
沒有 我問過了 現在我更急迫的需要這張沙發了
No, I already asked. Now I need this couch more than ever.
你還想犧牲多少人呢 Mike
How many people need to die, Mike?
- 沙發包在我們身上  - 就你們最好了
- We'll get you the couch. - You're the best!
我已經看上一款了 現在就去買
I already have one on hold. I'm gonna go get it right now.
噢 能借把傘嗎
Oh, hey, can I borrow your umbrella?
像要下雨了
It looks like it's gonna rain.
- 是啊 所以我也要用  - Michael 我才做完頭發
- Yeah, that's why I need it. - Michael, I just did my hair.
拿吧
Take the umbrella.
- 看吧 多簡單  - 那我用Eve的
- See, that was easy.  - And I'll just take Eve's umbrella.
又 見 彩 虹
第一季  第八集
電波誠譯
Henry先生 你全身濕透了
Mr. Henry, you're soaked.
你這樣的病能淋雨嗎
Can you be in the rain with your condition?
Kay 我只是有帕金森 又不是女巫
Kay, I have Parkinson's. I'm not a witch.
女巫 特指綠野仙蹤里被水濺到會融掉的女巫
我把健身房毛巾拿來 我不怎么出汗
I'll get you my gym towel. I barely perspired.
醫生說我汗腺小到危及生命的程度
The doctors say I have dangerously undersized sweat glands.
那你就別跑了啊 拜托
Well, then don't run, for Pete's sake.
- 喂  - 好消息 我買了張復古沙發
- Hello?   - Good news... I got a vintage couch,
所以省了點錢 壞消息是
so I saved us some money. Bad news...
仔細一看 沙發紋理
In the cold light of day, the upholstery pattern
看起來像一坨精子
looks like a bunch of sperms.
聽起來像佩斯利渦旋花紋 不錯啊
It sounds like paisley. It sounds fine.
沒事沒事 的確不錯
No, no, no, no, no. It's totally fine.
可這個"不錯" 是藥店網的牛仔褲那種"不錯"嗎
But is it fine like how drugstore jeans are fine?
藥店網 主營母嬰用品 保健品的購物網站
例如 紐扣把你肚子都壓淤青了
Like, when the buttons turn your belly green,
口袋都是畫上去的那種不錯嗎
and the pockets are just drawn on?
我是這么想的 翻新一下
Here's what I'm thinking... we reupholster...
- 是要花多點錢  - 夠了
- for just a little more money...   - All right, enough.
Leigh 我很愛你 可你
Leigh, I love you, but you
也該開始獨立生活了
have to start taking care of your own life.
選家私這種事你得自己來
You have to pick out your own upholstery.
別再跟寄生蟲似的了
The bloodsucking has to stop now.
嘿 飛濺山
Hey, splash mountain.
迪斯尼經典游戲項目 急流大峽谷泛舟
- 準備好開始大采訪沒  - 好了
- Ready for your big in-studio?   - Absolutely.
那你最好拿出渾身解數
Oh, you better bring your "A" Game
因為你要近距離接觸的是博士杰弗里...
because you're going toe-to-toe with Dr. Jeffrey...
刨你個底
Scratch-a-bottom.
一只貓 你讓我采訪一只貓
A cat? You want me to interview a cat?
它還能說"你好"
Well, it can say, "Hello."
你怎么說都行啦
That could be anything.
網絡上一致認為這是"你好"
Well, the internet decided it's "Hello."
我復出是要采訪人的
When I came out of retirement, it was to interview people
譬如德斯蒙德·圖圖 科里·布克或者紐約市長彭博
like Desmond Tutu and Cory Booker and Mayor Bloomberg.
德斯蒙德·圖圖 南非開普敦的圣公會前任大主教 科里·布克 美國新澤西州紐瓦克市長
反正前提是 人
It was, you know, humans.
這么說你不想采訪蘭斯·阿姆斯特朗的單車咯
So that's a "No" On interviewing Lance Armstrong's bike?
蘭斯·阿姆斯特朗 美國自行車名將
開玩笑的 我們怎么可能采訪的到頑強生命3000
No, I'm just kidding. We could never get Livestrong 3000.
頑強生命為阿姆斯特朗創辦的抗癌基金會 Harris誤把它當作阿姆斯特朗的坐騎
好吧 我不會虧待你的
All right. Well, I'll get you something good.
我保證 趕緊去采訪這貓吧
I promise. Now go interview this cat.
是吧 很干的 你真該看看我在桑拿房是怎樣的
See? Bone dry. You should see me in a sauna.
剛剛這話欠考慮是嗎
Was that inappropriate?
你想聊點什么呢
So what do you want to talk about?
喵
Vrr!
惡作劇有點樣子嘛
Nice try on the prank.
我看到你包在馬桶上的保鮮膜了
I found the saran wrap you put on the toilet.
戳了個小洞 有八成都流下去了
Poked a hole in it. 80% went right through.
- 你竟然沒把它拿掉  - 我干活用腦子 不是蠻力
- You didn't take it off?   - I work smart. Not hard.
我現在沒空跟你玩了
I don't have time for this anyway.
網上的簡歷有回復了
I got a bite on my online resume.
明晚我要和一個"噢真的嗎總裁"吃飯
I'm having dinner tomorrow night with the C-E-Oh-no-he-didn't.
可他真聯系我了 我們要一起吃晚餐
But, yes, he did. We're really having dinner.
保鮮膜不過是個障眼法
The saran wrap was a decoy prank.
真正的惡作劇是那個總裁 其實根本沒有總裁
The real prank is the CEO, because there is no CEO.
一切都是我策劃的
I set the whole thing up.
真替你高興 Ian
I'm really proud of you,Ian.
你就要飛上枝頭了
You are on a rocket ride to the top.
- 這可不是我說的  - 洗手間有個強勁力場
- Your words.   - There's a force field on the toilet!
媽咪
Mom!
跟你說 今天拒絕Leigh的感覺真好
I tell you, it felt so good to stand up to Leigh today.
我感覺到有股力量在我體內流串
I can feel the power coursing... through my body.
回家時 我僅用念力叫到了輛的士
On the way home, I hailed a cab using only the power of my mind.
Mike 你不過就在電話里跟你妹說了"不"
Mike, you said "No" To your sister over the phone.
而你舉的重量是我在芭蕾班用的
And you're using the weights I use in ballet class.
我還帶了你的腳環 看
I'm also using your anklets. Look out.
好了 首先 我沒在生你氣
Okay, first off, I'm not mad at you.
- 噢 挺好的  - 可那張你拒絕翻新的
- Well, that's good to know.   - But that couch
沙發 滿都是臭蟲
you wouldn't reupholster? It's full of bed bugs.
- Leigh 這太糟了  - 是啊 我在上面睡了十分鐘
- Leigh, that's horrible.   - Yeah, I fell asleep on that thing
醒來全身都被咬了
for ten minutes... woke up covered in bites.
我只好脫光衣服洗個超燙熱水澡
I had to strip down, take a searing hot shower,
然后赤條條低頭跑進洗衣房拿毛巾
and crouch-run naked to the laundry room to get a towel.
剛好碰見搶手貨Roland 他竟然看都不看我一眼
Went right by Roland "The Super" Who didn't even look up,
- 明顯是同性戀  - 妥妥的
- so he is obviously a gay.   - That would do it...
太可怕了 我所有的東西都在下面呢
This is a disaster! Everything I own is down there.
我的湯匙
My spoons...
只是舉個例子 我太精疲力盡沒法一樣樣說了
That's just one example. I'm too frazzled to make a list.
好吧 先披一下
Okay, all right, let's get you covered up,
看你浴巾快卷上去了
'cause I'm getting a little up-towel action.
Mike 我也不想拜托你的
Mike, you know I hate to ask you,
- 但旅館太貴了 - 不 不 不
- but hotels are expensive... - No, no, no.
我不會出旅館住宿費的 你是成年人了
I'm not paying for a hotel. You're an adult.
- 這個問題你自己可以解決的 - 你說的對
- You can solve this problem on your own. - You're right.
我只能多忍忍
I'm just gonna have to suck it up and...
- 和你們擠擠了 - 這肯定比住旅館便宜
- stay with you. - It'd be cheaper than a hotel.
- 她可以睡沙發 - 挺不錯嘛 真的
- She could take the couch. - That's great, you know.
等下 小孩兒們一般幾點起床
Wait, what time do the kids get up again?
- 因為我比較喜歡裸睡 - 還是我睡沙發吧
- Because I'm a pretty naked sleeper. - I'll take the couch.
你怎么穿粉色的沙袋
You're wearing pink ankle weights?
你們到底有什么怪癖啊
What kind of stuff are you guys into?
Priscilla Priscilla Priscilla
Priscilla, Priscilla, Priscilla...
打包好東西 你得走了
Pack your bags. It's time for your exit.
她說你假 打她的假胸
She called you fake! Punch her in the implants.
這演的什么 <唐頓莊園>嗎
- What is this, Downton Abbey?
– <壞女孩俱樂部> 是為了工作
- Bad Girls Club. For work.
我得寫在線摘要
I have to write my online recap.
<每周娛樂> 稱其是徹頭徹尾的垃圾
Entertainment Weekly called them "Total garbage."
那啥 至少你吸引他們注意了
Well, at least you're on their radar.
我得趕緊把電視關了
I gotta turn this off
在孩子們看到人生中第一個乳環之前
before the kids see their first nipple ring.
- 你剛把這個遙控器生出來的嗎 - 只是乳液而已
- What, did you give birth to that? - It's just a little lotion.
我或許遺傳了我們家的個子
I may have gotten all the height in the family,
- 但你遺傳了所有的濕度 - 對 我真是幸運
- but you got all the moisture. - Yeah, I'm genetically blessed.
- 除蟲那事兒怎么樣了 - 我懂的 小濕濕
- So where are we on exterminator? - I get it, moisty.
你想讓我走 別擔心 我會走的
You want me out. Don't worry. I'm on it.
- 早啊 - 早啊
- Mornin'. - Morning.
- 你頭發里有根芝士條 - 什么
- You have a cheese doodle in your hair. - What?
- 芝士條 - 芝士條
- Doodle. - Doodle.
你現在還不后悔拒絕了Leigh嗎
So you're still glad you said "No" To Leigh?
我要是剛開始沒答應給她買沙發
I wouldn't have had to say
就沒這么多事兒了
"No" If I hadn't said "Yes" To the couch.
再說了 這是誰的主意來著
Remind me again, whose idea was that?
噢 我記不清了 但是她這主意挺不錯的
Oh, I can't remember, but she sounds cool.
我得睡一晚上沙發上算什么
Who cares if I had to spend a night on the couch?
我覺得 重要的是
I mean, the important thing
我不再對她有求必應 她才能學到教訓
is I said "No" To her, and she's learning.
- 那她學到沒 - 最終 她會的
- Is she? - She will. Eventually.
孩子一天沒有學好 你就會放棄這個學生嗎
Would you give up on a student after one bad day?
常事兒啊 第一天午飯之前
All the time... by lunch on the first day,
我就對五個熊孩子視而不見了
five kids are dead to me.
你瞧 這就是為啥我比你更適合做老師
See, this is why I'm a better teacher than you.
- 噢 芝士條都軟了 – 對 惡心死了
- Oh, that went completely soft. - Yeah, it was disgusting.
這是什么 是我的簡歷
What's this? Just my resume.
白色亞麻 八十磅雙壓花紙
Double embossed on white linen 80-pound card stock.
挺多高中社團嘛 不錯嘛
A lot of high school clubs on here. Impressive.
是為了和那個超高機密的剛起步公司老總會面準備的
It's for my meeting with the head of a top secret start-up.
我想谷歌一下他 但是
I tried to google him, but there's,
有幾百萬個叫David Johnsons的
like, a million David Johnsons.
我可不是新手
I'm not new at this.
這寫著你能夠流利使用法語進行日常對話
It says here you speak conversational French.
我在法國活下去沒問題
I could survive in Paris.
對(法語)
Oui.
我說的可不是法語
I wasn't speaking French.
是的 這真是好消息 謝謝了
Yeah, that's great news. Thanks.
太好了 太好了 滅蟲的人今天就能來
Yes. Yes! Exterminator's coming today.
她這周末就能走了 再也不用睡沙發了
She'll be out at the end of the week. No more couch sleeping!
是的 Mike 真是不錯 真是不錯
Yeah, Mike. That's great, that's great.
但是 你在鏡頭里
But you're in the shot.
你一邊指著這些注釋
If you could just point at these notes
- 一邊慢慢走開 - 快點
- while we walk away... - Come on.
抱歉 我太高興了 只是剛剛知道苦日子要結束了
Sorry, I'm in a good mood. Just knowing the end is near
- 感覺一切都沒那么難以忍受了 - 是啊
- makes it all seem bearable. - Yeah.
感覺就跟平胸女人調情一樣
Like going to a play with a flat-chested woman.
你看這兒 看看她對我的襪子做了什么
Look at this. Look what she does to my socks.
她穿了我的襪子 用她那巨腳丫子把我襪子都撐變形了
She puts them on her big, giant feet and she stretches them out.
你看這火雞都這樣了 你看看
Look at this turkey gobble. Look at that.
這么多松松垮垮的地方
Yeah, so much saggy material.
就好像是平胸女人的襯衣一樣
Like a blouse on a flat-chested woman.
你昨晚的約會咋樣了
How'd your date go last night?
還行吧 嗨 聽好了
The play was all right. Hey, look.
這次我找了個正經采訪
I got a real interview this time.
明天你跟克里斯·克里斯帝面對面專訪
Tomorrow you're going toe-to-toe with Chris Christie.
新澤西州州長
- 真的嗎 - 是的
- No, really? - Yeah.
- 真是太棒了 - 是啊
- That's fantastic! - Yeah.
- 我得好好準備下 - 好的
- I gotta go prepare. - All right.
如果到頭來成專訪穿風衣的貓
If this turns out to be a cat in a windbreaker,
- 我會殺了你 - Mike 你在鏡頭里
- I'm gonna murder you. - Mike, you're in the shot!
我睡覺的時候你吐我床上了
You're throwing in my bed while I'm sleeping.
- 噢 - 好了 別再看壞女孩俱樂部了
- Oh! - Okay, enough bad girls club.
我要在客廳工作了
I'm gonna be working in the dining room.
我要準備一個重要專訪...
I gotta prepare my big interview with...
噓 Cheyenne正說話呢
Shh! Cheyenne is talking.
什么 Leigh讓你跟著一起看這個了嗎
What, has Aunt Leigh got you watching this too?
你不是還有論文要寫嗎
Don't you have a paper to write?
她的假發落在告解室了
Her weave is in the confessional.
等一下 她剛剛是不是把頭發拿下來了
Wait a minute, did she just take her hair off?
只是丑斃的假發而已 老爸
It's just a busted-ass weave, Dad.
- "孔雀裝逼"開始了 - "孔雀裝逼"啥意思
- Let the peacocking begin. - What the hell is "Peacocking"?
就是你給高檔西服上配上浮夸的配件
It's when you add a flashy accessory to an upscale suit.
這可是工作面試時候活絡話題的法寶
It's an instant conversation starter at a job interview.
好吧 容我先說一說
Well, let me start a conversation...
你買西服哪兒來的錢
Where'd you get the money to buy the suit?
我把奶奶給我的儲蓄債券兌現了
Oh, I cashed in the savings bond Grandma gave me.
是罰了一點款 是因為還沒到期
There was a penalty because it hadn't matured.
但我覺得時機已到 謝謝你的建議 Leigh姑姑
But I have. Thanks for the advice, Aunt Leigh.
如果你想脫穎而出 著裝就得先脫穎而出啊
If you want to stand out in business, you have to look the part.
必須先花了錢 才能去掙錢
You gotta spend money to make money.
不 不 必須先掙了錢 才有錢去花
No. No, see, you have to make money to spend money.
孔雀叫著 要飛走了
That's a peacock sound. Gotta fly.
孔雀可不會飛
Peacocks don't fly.
嗨 老爸 你看見我ipod沒
Hey, Dad. Have you seen my iPod?
哇擦 伙計 你這是干嘛
Whoa, buddy. What are you doing?
咱可不允許在家里裸奔
We don't walk around the house naked.
可以的 今天早上我看到Leigh姑姑
Oh, yeah, we do. I saw Aunt Leigh this morning
在廚房里光著身子喝橙汁呢
chugging orange juice in the kitchen naked.
別搞笑了
Turn it up!
Leigh開始掌控這個家了 我有兩個選擇
Leigh had taken over the house. I had two options...
直面這個問題或者
Confront the problem directly or...
你就在這兒準備克里斯蒂的專訪嗎
This is where you're prepping for your Christie interview?
是的 在這兒能靜下心來 要是我餓了
Yeah, it's easier to focus in here, and if I get hungry,
- 百花包里還有酸果蔓 - 我明白了
- there's dried cranberry in the potpourri. - I see.
更輕松的辦法是你直接付了Leigh翻新沙發的錢
A lazy mind might think that it would've been easier
就沒這么多事兒了
for you to just buy Leigh that upholstery.
那還有什么教育意義呢
Where would the lesson be in that?
- 我已經打破這個惡性循環了 - 是的 是的
- I've broken the cycle, honey. - Yes. Yes, you have.
我也就只是犧牲了幾晚上睡沙發
And all it cost me was a couple nights on a sofa
早上特早起來和在廁所辦公
and getting up extra early and working in the bathroom
還有在衣籃上打字 天 求你了 寶貝
and typing on a hamper... oh, god, please, honey.
你得幫幫我 快擺脫掉她
You gotta help me. You gotta get rid of her.
好吧 好吧 我今晚把她帶出去
Okay, okay, okay. Um... I'll take her out tonight.
帶她喝點酒 把她軟化然后
I will soften her up with a few drinks and then
我在慢慢的建議她 趕緊麻溜的閃人
I will gently suggest that she get the hell out of here.
但是有句話得說明白 這些我提前都猜到了
But just for the record, I predicted all of this.
- 連廁所都猜到了 - 不 這個算是額外驚喜
- Even the toilet? - No, that was just a fun bonus.
Fonz的辦公室也是在廁所的
Just so you know, the Fonz's office was in a bathroom.
電視連續劇中角色 他把附近一家漢堡包連鎖店的男廁所當作自己的辦公室
- 寶貝 你跟Fonz差遠了 - 嗨
- Honey, you are so not the Fonz. - Hey.
謝謝
Thank you.
整蠱Ian太容易了 因為他太過自信
It's easy to prank Ian because he's so sure of himself.
總是出錯 卻從不懷疑
Often wrong, never in doubt.
計劃是讓他最終放棄無奈的向服務員要賬單
The plan was for him to eventually give up and ask for the check.
然后我叫服務員拿給他
Then I'd have the waitress bring him
一個奶酪棒和一頂水手帽
a single mozzarella stick and a sailor cap.
整蠱成功
Sha-boof.
我本以為這會很有趣
It was supposed to be funny.
但是并沒有
But it wasn't.
噓 Mike明天有個很重要的采訪
Shh. Mike has a very big interview tomorrow.
我知道怎么溜進漆黑的房間里
I think I know how to sneak into a dark apartment.
哦 這東西什么時候在那兒的
Oh, that came out of nowhere.
- 嗨 - 現在可是凌晨兩點了
- Hi. - It's 2:00 in the morning!
隨便了 Mike大本鐘
Whatever, Mike o'Clock.
這確實搞笑 因為你不是愛爾蘭人
Okay, that... that is funny because you are not Irish.
- 啥 - 還有我們都喝多了
- Huh? - Also 'cause we're drunk.
每次我們一接吻
The bartender gave us
酒保就請我們喝酒
free drinks every time we kissed each other.
這下好了 你喚醒了"大學Annie"
Oh, great, you reawakened "College Annie."
不 大學Annie會伸舌頭的
Oh, no. "College Annie" Would've used tongue.
- 我會的 - 我老婆跟我妹接吻
- I would have. - My wife is kissing my sister.
這真是 真是好玩 你知道還有啥好玩不
That's... that's fun. You know what else is fun?
立馬上床睡覺 我必須得睡覺了
Going to bed immediately. I've got to get some sleep.
你確定一定以及肯定是對的
You are absolutely, totally right.
我們馬上就去
And we are gonna pull it together for you.
- 比薩 比薩到了  - 噢
- Pizza! Pizza! - Oh, pucker up!
我想要免費的長棍面包
I want free crazy bread.
- 不行 別親了  - 嗨 比薩小子
- No! No kissing for bread! - Hey, Mr. Pizza man.
你到底死哪去了 還有五分鐘就開始了
Where the hell have you been? We're on in 5 minutes!
氣色不錯 Henry先生 我不能騙你
Looking good, Mr. Henry. I can't lie to you.
你看起來像在溝里過了一夜
You look like you slept in a ditch.
昨晚我沒睡好 我妹妹親了我老婆
I didn't get much sleep last night. My sister kissed my wife
在沙發上把面包吐得到處都是
and then threw up crazy bread all over the couch.
什么 你辦了派對卻沒邀請我
Oh, so you had a party and didn't invite me?
走吧 我們去吧
Let's go, let's do this.
- 不不不  - 這邊
- Oh! No, no, no, no. - Okay, well...
他在這邊 攝影機和燈光都在那邊
he's over here where all the cameras and the lights are.
- 早上好 州長先生  - Mike 幸會
- Hello, Governor. - Mike, great to see you.
- 謝謝你們請我來  - 我的榮幸
- Thanks for having me on. - My pleasure.
- 很好  - 你握得太用力了
- Great. - You're crushing my hand.
- 抱歉  - 大家好 我是Mike Henry
- Oh, sorry. - Hello, I'm Mike Henry.
今天我們將對話新澤西州長
Today we'll be speaking to the Governor of New Jersey,
克里斯·克里斯帝先生
Chris Christie. Governor,
- 歡迎你  - 謝謝你 Mike
- welcome. - Mike, thanks for having me.
很高興看到你重返崗位
I'm so glad to see you back doing your job.
你知道嗎 我認為你的經歷非常激勵人
And, you know, I find your story just so inspiring...
事實上 我認為你是勵志的楷模
in fact, I think it's so inspiring.
社會上有許多傳聞
There's been a lot of speculation
我今天受到你的鼓舞
about things, and I feel so inspired today.
想做一個公開說明 那么 Mike
I think I should make an announcement. So Mike...
叫醒他
Wake him up!
嗨
Hi.
松餅
Muffins!
我們等等再討論這個問題
Uh... Well, we'll get to that question later.
我何必費這個心呢
Why do I even bother?
- 哦  - 某人喝瘋了哈
- Oh... - Someone's got a hangover.
不 只是派對和快樂時光過后的惡心頭痛而已
No, just a little party headache with some good-time nausea.
- 你在做什么  - 給我和Ian煎蛋
- What are you doing? - Making omelets for me and Ian.
噢 真體貼
Oh, that's sweet.
我希望你爸爸和你姑姑也這么友愛
I wish your father and your aunt were as close as you.
嘿 這個長棍面包哪來的
Hey, where'd this crazy bread come from?
- 你真不記得了  - 我現在正需要它
- You seriously don't remember? - This is exactly what I need.
我就是...不 不 再等等
I just... oh, god, no. Whoa, too soon. Too soon.
- 來個煎蛋嗎  - 你剛坐在上面了吧
- Want an omelet? - You probably put your butt on them,
我對屁股味的煎蛋不太感興趣 還是算了吧
and since I'm not partial to butt omelets, I shall pass.
你看起來心情不錯啊
You seem to be in a good mood.
Johnson昨晚沒出現
Johnson was actually a no-show last night,
但是他發了郵件來道歉
but I got an email from him apologizing.
我不能對他太殘忍
I had to let him down easy.
他說如果不是昨天搬到波基普西去了的話
He said I'd have been an Insta-hire
一定會果斷錄用我
if they'd not just relocated to Poughkeepsie last night.
也許這樣最好
Well, maybe it's for the best.
- 所以我要去波基普西  - 等等 什么
- So I'm going to Poughkeepsie. - Wait, what?
不好意思 我要去趕火車了
Now if you'll excuse me, I have a train to catch.
等等 Ian
Wait... Ian?!
Leigh 我們一定要 天哪這是什么
Leigh, we have to ta... Oh, what is that?
鋼管舞
Pole dancing.
可以激發潛能 而且對脊柱也很有好處
It's so empowering, and it's really good for your core.
你是怎么 算了
How did you... nevermind.
聽著 我在早上一整個重要的采訪中 都昏昏欲睡
Look, I fell asleep during my big interview with...
旋轉下剪式
Scissor grab!
- 我能感受到身體在燃燒 Mike  - 去樓下燒吧
- I can really feel the burn, Mike. - Take the burn downstairs.
既然驅蟲的人走了 你可以回去了
It should be aired out now the exterminator's gone.
那家伙來過 但他沒噴藥
Oh, the exterminator came, but he didn't spray.
- 他沒什么  - 他告訴我藥劑有毒的時候
- He didn't what?! - When he told me how
我就讓他哪來回哪去了
toxic that stuff was, I sent him on his way.
真希望有一種毒藥
Hopefully to get an even deadlier chemical
可以讓你快點離開這里
that will get you out of here faster.
別擔心 我的營養師說 要燒鼠尾草
Don't worry. My nutritionist said to burn sage.
通常需要兩到三星期
It usually takes about two to three weeks.
"兩到三星期" 還是你的營養師說的
"Two to three weeks"? And this time line is coming
這真是 毫無意義
from your nutritionist, so it means... nothing!
冷靜 Mike 臭蟲又不是在你床上
Calm down, Mike. You'd think you were the one with bed bugs.
它確實在 Leigh 就是你
I do have bed bugs, Leigh. You're my bed bug!
你闖進我家里 擾亂我的家人 毀了我的生活
You've infested my house, you've destroyed our lives,
我告訴你 現在就給我走
I've gotta get you out of here now!
這是唯一一個你沒有放乳液的地方
That's the only thing in this house you haven't put lotion on.
就是這樣 我自己來搞定
That's it. I'm doing it myself.
- 什么  - 那個驅蟲的家伙手上有活
- What? - The exterminator was booked.
所以我給了他一百塊 他給了我殺蟲劑
So I slipped him 100 bucks. He gave me the pesticides.
氧氣罐有了 噴霧器有了
I got bombs, I got sprays,
放汽車電池里那玩意也有了
I got the stuff they put in car batteries.
硫酸
你居然還在床上躺著啊
Are you seriously still in bed?
這就是你拒絕Leigh的下場
This is what happens when you say "No" To Leigh.
這是和Leigh一起灌酒的下場吧
This is what happens when you drink Jager shots with Leigh.
這就是你的保護措施
That's all the protection you're using?
我大腦都損傷了 一點點化學藥劑能奈我何
I got a brain disease. What are a few chemicals gonna do to me?
Ian Ian
Ian! Ian!
- Ian  - Eve 你來這做什么
- Ian! - Eve, what are you doing here?
根本沒David Johnson這人 是我編的
There is no David Johnson. I made it up.
只是為了報復你
This was my prank to get you back.
我從沒想過會變成這樣
I-I never meant for it to get this far.
我感覺糟透了
I feel terrible.
得了吧
Nice try.
通往波基普西的19次列車即將開啟
All aboard track 19 for Poughkeepsie.
得走了 下次再見
Gotta run. See you when I see you.
看著Ian 我不再感到愧疚了
Watching Ian, I didn't feel bad anymore.
我開始嫉妒他
I was actually jealous.
他也許還沒想好未來的事 但一旦他想清楚了
He might not have it all figured out, but once he does,
就沒有什么能夠阻擋他
there is absolutely nothing that'll stop him.
柏金森疾病
這會讓你的臉年輕十歲
This will take ten years off your face.
可我才八歲呢
But I'm only eight.
Leigh姑姑在給我們敷泥面膜 你想來嗎
Aunt Leigh is making us all mud masks. You want one?
- 你不是還有論文要寫嗎  - 寫完了
- Don't you still have a paper to write? - I finished it.
整整八頁 關于真人秀的上癮問題
Eight pages on the addictive qualities of reality TV.
我從來沒這么高效過
I've never been more productive
因為獎勵是繼續看<壞女孩俱樂部>
because my reward was more bad girls club.
原來知識本身不是獎勵
I guess knowledge isn't its own reward.
"孔雀裝逼裝"得到了回報
So the peacocking paid off.
當時我在去波基普西的火車上
I was on the train to Poughkeepsie,
- 說來話長  - 那就跳過
- long story... - Don't need to hear it.
有個家伙說他喜歡我的穿衣風格
When this guy said he liked my style.
原來他是<今日男士>的職員
Turns out he works for Today's Man.
我稍稍施展魅力 砰 工作搞定
So I turned up the charm, and sha-dank! Job offer...
- 銷售合伙人  - 所以你現在是個西裝銷售員了
- sales associate. - So you're a suit salesman?
不 我是西裝贈送員
No, I'm a suit givesman
因為我們基本上是白送 砰
because we're basically just giving them away. Boom!
第一個月的月租
First month's rent.
我猜你這是你的功勞
Wow. I suppose you had something to do with this.
不 這都是他自己的能耐
No, he did this all on his own.
沒錯 也許Leigh總是無事不登三寶殿
Sure, maybe Leigh only comes up here when she wants something.
但有時候她想要的不過是
But sometimes that something...
和她的家人待在一起而已
is just to be around her family.
聽著 我知道我一直招你嫌
Hey, listen, I know I've been a giant pain in the ass.
所以我會趕緊把房子弄清楚 不來煩你了
So I'm just gonna get cleaned up, and I'll be out of your way.
Leigh 為啥會刺痛啊
Leigh, are these supposed to tingle?
這就說明辣椒有用啊
That's how you know the cayenne pepper's working.
我在想是不是沒人知道里邊還有辣椒啊
I'm guessing no one knew about the cayenne pepper.
這很好 就像把臉塞在螞蟻窩里一樣爽
It's great. It's like sticking your face in an anthill.
好了 快點 把這個洗掉
Okay, let's go, guys. Let's take these off.
你們不能敷到一半就
People, you can't jump midstream. It'll never...
- 啊  - 天哪 弄到鼻子里了
- Aah! - Oh, god, it's up my nose.
在我鼻子里 在我鼻子里
It's in my nose! It's in my nose!
很適合你的形象
That's a good look for you.
你皮膚看起來好極了 對鼻竇很有好處的
Your skin looks so good! Really good for your sinuses.
兄弟姐妹真的很奇妙
That's the weird thing about siblings.
他們一輩子都在你身邊
They're with you your whole life...
- 我們停戰吧  - 行啊
- Can we call a truce on the prank war? - Course. Oh.
對了 我給你帶了一罐花生糖
And by the way, I got you a can of peanut brittle.
即使你認為你了解他們
And even though you think you know them...
是啊 "花生糖"
Uh-huh. Okay. "Peanut brittle."
他們還是會讓你驚訝
They still surprise you.
聽著 我一直在想
Listen, I've been thinking.
驅蟲那事兒 我認為鼠尾草是最佳選擇
About the bed bug thing, I think sage is the responsible choice.
我只是想告訴你 在這個家
I just want you to know that you're welcome to stay
- 你想待多久就待多久 - 謝謝 Mike
- here as long as you want. - Thanks, Mike. Really.
不過我要去Carol那住了
But I'm going to crash at Carol's.
我真的愛你的家人 不過他們真太累人了
I really love your family, but they can be exhausting.
我只能付出到這程度了
I can only give so much, you know.
一直有Carol家這個選擇嗎
Was Carol's always an option?
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組